const questions = [

    {
      question: "Which of the following should you NOT do during a fire emergency?",
      options: ["Re-enter the building without the permission of authorities", "Keep fire doors shut to prevent the fire from spreading", "Crawl low under the smoke while breathing only through your nose", "Evacuate a building through designated exit routes"],
      correct: "Re-enter the building without the permission of authorities"
    },
    {
      question: "Electrical panel rooms may be entered by",
      options: ["Any employee", "Authorized employees", "Housekeeper", "Management employees"],
      correct: "Authorized employees"
    },
    {
      question: "You may only operate equipment",
      options: ["If you are sure you will not get hurt", "Are trained and authorized", "If no one else knows the procedures", "None of the above"],
      correct: "Are trained and authorized"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is primarily responsible for providing employees with a fall protection system?",
      options: ["The manufacturer of the fall protection system", "The employee", "The employer", "The insurer"],
      correct: "The employer"
    },
    {
      question: "Where should you aim a fire extinguisher nozzle when putting out a fire?",
      options: ["At the top of the fire", "At the center of the fire", "Away from the fire", "At the base of the fire"],
      correct: "At the base of the fire"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following should you NOT do while treating cuts and scrapes?",
      options: [
        "Apply pressure on the wound with a clean cloth or bandage",
        "Wash the wound with soap",
        "Apply an antibiotic to the wound",
        "Cover the wound"
      ],
      correct: "Cover the wound"
    },
    {
      question: "Riders are allowed on forklifts",
      options: [
        "If they hang on with both hands",
        "If they are licensed to operate forklifts",
        "Never",
        "If they ride on the back"
      ],
      correct: "Never"
    },
    {
      question: "Modification to forklifts must be approved by",
      options: [
        "The manufacturer",
        "By the Operator",
        "By a Supervisor",
        "By Management"
      ],
      correct: "The manufacturer"
    },
    {
      question: "The last step in Lockout-Tagout is",
      options: [
        "Attempt to start the equipment",
        "Tell the equipment operator",
        "Inform management",
        "Open the equipment"
      ],
      correct: "Attempt to start the equipment"
    },
    {
      question: "On the multi-colored chemical label, Yellow represents",
      options: [
        "Fire Hazard",
        "Health Hazard",
        "Reactivity Hazard",
        "Personal Protective Equipment"
      ],
      correct: "Reactivity Hazard"
    },
  ];
  
  export default questions;
  